AMRENDRA SINGH

3/852 Vastu Khand Gomti Nagar Lucknow 226010, India.

**** +91-8004804008.** E-mail: <u>amrendra911@gmail.com.</u>

Date:
Dear, Sir/ Ma'am,
I am writing to express my interest of working with your organization as in Sales and Marketing, please accept my resume for your consideration. With over 12 years' experience in Sales and Marketing,
My achievements are:-
> CANVERA DIGITAL TECHNOLOGIES PVT LTD, got KAL Samman Superstar Award in Aug & Sep in 2016, and also working as a one of the Higher Target Revenue Achiever Relationship Executive in whole Uttar Pradesh.
Selected as a Best Sales Executives within Six Months from Trend Marketing Lucknow and get awarded in 76 th Best Sales Executives from all over INDIA of Canon INDIA Pvt in 2013, event in Delhi.
Promoted as a Team Leader within Seven months for HDFC Bank Mohan Cooperative Branch in Delhi in 2012.
I am confident that my contributions would be a valuable asset.
I have considerable experience in all areas of Sales & Marketing, i consider myself to be professional dependable, considerate and smart-working.
My resume, which i have enclosed for your review, contains additional detail about my professional expertise. I look forward to the opportunity to discuss the qualifications i would bring to your organization. Thank you for your consideration.
Sincerely,
Amrendra Singh
Enclosure: Resume

CURRICULUM-VITAE

AMRENDRA SINGH



CONTACT:

3/852 Vastu Khand Gomti Nagar Lucknow 226010, India.

+91-8004804008.

E-mail: amrendra911@gmail.com

PROFILE:

OBJECTIVE

To render my loyal services to your prestigious organization from all the experience and training i have gained throughout my academics in the college as well as in job.

EXPERIENCE:

CANVERA DIGITAL TECHNOLOGIES PVT LTD

(03rd Oct 2013 – Present) in Lucknow.

- **▶** Working as Key Account Leader. (B2B,Channel sales)
- > Working Areas: Lucknow, Sultanpur, Faizabad and Raebareli.
- > COMPANY PROFILE: (Online photography company providing mass customized printed products and e-commerce solutions to professional photographers)
- **DURATION**: (03rd Oct 2013 31st Oct 2023)
- ➤ **JOB DESCRIPTION:** To enhance the business of professional photographers and sales generation, giving presentations to clients, provide product knowledge & solving customer queries, collect customer information and provide reports to Sales Supervisor.

CANON INDIA (17th July 2012 – 30th Sep 2013) in Lucknow.

- > Working as Sales Executive with channel partner Trend Marketing. (Corporate sales).
- **COMPANY PROFILE: Consumer Electronics. (OIS,Personal or business multi-function devices)**
- **DURATION**: (17th July 2012 30th Sep 2013)
- ▶ **JOB DESCRIPTION:** Selling Multi-Function devices like Color and black & white printer and photocopiers, etc,(DGS&D tenders for Government sectors, Institutional sales, Corporate deals) Sales Generation, giving presentations to clients, collect customer information, provide product knowledge & solving customer queries and provide reports to Sales Manager.

HDFC BANK (20th Aug 2011 - 31st March 2012) in DELHI.

- ➤ Working as Senior Sales Officer. (Direct SalesLiability)
- **COMPANY PROFILE:** Banking.
- **DURATION**: (20th Aug 2011 31st March 2012)
- **JOB DESCRIPTION:** Sales Generation, giving presentations to clients, collect customer information, provide product knowledge & solving customer queries and provide reports to Sales Manager.

COMPUTER KNOWLEDGE:

- > SOFTWARE: Ms-Office, Premier Pro, Final Cut Pro, Photoshop, Coral Draw.
- > LANGUAGES: C, C++, Ms-Dos,
- ➤ OPERATING SYSTEMS: Dos, Microsoft Windows, Mac os.

PROFESSIONAL QULIFICATIONS:

- ➤ M.B.A IN (MARKETING) & PGPPE IN (HR) SPECIALIZATION, from "rai business school" New Delhi. Which is affiliated to MAHARISHI DAYANAND UNIVERSITY, ROHATAK HARAYANA 2008-2010
- **B.B.A.** from Lucknow University, Lucknow in 2004 -07.
- ➤ DIPLOMA IN ADCA. From Standard Multimedia Computer Centre, Lucknow in 2008-09.
- ➤ DIPLOMA IN D.T.P. from Gaurav Computer Social & Economic Dev-Inst-India, Lucknow in 2002

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION:

- > S.S.C (SCIENCE) from Little Angles High School Indira Nagar, Lucknow up in 2001 -02.
- ➤ H.S.C (COMMERCE) from Rasphil Academy Adil Nagar, Lucknow up in 2003 04.

PERSONAL DETAILS:

DATE OF BIRTH : 25th July 1985

FATHER'S NAME : Mr. Bhopal Singh

MOTHER'S NAME : Mrs. Suresh Bala

SEX : Male

MARITAL STATUS : Married

I hereby declare that the above information is true and genuine to the best of my knowledge.

Date: (Signature)

Place: AMRENDRA SINGH